[Music]
you have always made the right choices
in life right from prioritizing your
goals to embracing new changes from
creating a safety net for your family to
making each of their wishes a
reality so why not make the right choice
to secure your retirement
goals with ICICI Pro guaranteed pension
plans guaranteed income for life it's
time you say I am Future Ready
guaranteed pension plan is a flexible
plan that offers multiple options for
someone planning to
retire it guarantees a regular stream of
income throughout their life to ensure
they continue to live life on their own
terms ICICI Pro guaranteed pension plan
is your best option to plan retirement
as it
offers guaranteed lifelong annuity where
you pay just once and get guaranteed
regular annuity for your entire life
along with an option to defer annuity by
up to 10 years an option to receive
annuity income either monthly quarterly
half yearly or
yearly an option for single life or
joint life
cover and multiple plan options to
choose from you can choose the plan that
suits your lifestyle and future needs
best let's understand the plan and plan
options in detail Rahul is a 55-year-old
professional approaching retirement he
wants to create an immediate source of
income for himself so that he gets
guaranteed annuity to take care of his
needs in his postretirement
years Rahul can choose from multiple
annuity options single life without
return of purchase price joint life
without return of purchase price single
life with return of purchase price joint
life with return of purchase price
single life with return of purchase
price at age
80 single life with 50% return of
purchase price at age
80 single life with return of purchase
price from the age of
76 single life with return of purchase
price on critical
illness or permanent disability due to
accident or death death deferred single
life with return of purchase price
deferred joint life with return of
purchase
price deferred single life with return
of purchase price on critical
illness or permanent disability due to
accident or
death let's take a closer look at a few
of these options first is single life
without return of purchase price where
he pays a single premium at the start of
the plan and receives an annuity
immediately which continues for
Life the second option is single life
with return of purchase price at age 80
where he not only receives regular
annuity but also the purchase price or
premium is paid to him as he turns 80
years old let us say that he takes the
planet aged 60 and pays 20 lakh rupees
as a single premium immediately he will
start receiving annuity of 9
9,582 rupees every year on turning 80 he
will receive a return of purchase of 20
lakh rupees and the annuity of
9,582 rupees every year
continues the third option is single
life with 50% return of purchase price
at age
80 if he takes the planet age 60 he pays
20 lakh rupees as a single premium
immediately he will start receiving
annuity of
1,372 rupees every
year at 80 he will receive a 50% return
of purchase of 10 lakh Rupees and the
annuity of 1ak 110,000 372 rupees
continues every year in case of his
unfortunate demise during the annuity
period the remaining 50% return of
purchase of 10 lakh Rupees will be paid
out to his nom
then there is single life with return of
purchase price from the age of 76 where
5% of the purchase price starts getting
paid out in addition to his annuity on
attaining age
76 if he takes the plan at age 60 he
pays 20 lakh rupees as a single premium
immediately he will start receiving
annuity of 1
7,452 rupe every year at 7 6 he will
receive an additional 1 lakh rupees
every year which is 5% of the purchase
along with the annuity of 1
7,452 rupe every
year the balanced purchase price if any
is paid out to the nominee in case of
his unfortunate
demise the last option is deferred
single life with return of purchase
price on critical illness Ci or
permanent disability
[Music]
health problems and critical illnesses
are rising every day to help tackle
expenses regarding health or any
disability this option pays back the
premium on the diagnosis of any critical
illness or permanent disability due to
an
accident if he takes the planet age 45
he pays 20 lakh rupees as a single
premium after the end of the deferment
period of 10 years he will start
receiving annuity of 2
42,5 123 rupe every year for life in
case he's diagnosed with a critical
illness or permanent disability he will
receive a return of purchase of 20 lakh
rupees let's say Rahul is a 40-year-old
professional looking to plan for his
retirement he may want a deferred
annuity plan to create a CPUs for his
post-retirement years he can choose a
deferment period from 1 to 10 years post
the deferment period he will start
receiving annuity every year he will
also get to choose from the Deferred
annuity options and select either
annuity with return of purchase price
for single or joint life or life annuity
with return of purchase on critical
illness or permanent disability due to
accident for single
life besides the multiple annuity
options
this plan provides a topup facility
feature where he can increase his
annuity by paying an additional
premium finally there is the high
purchase price benefit through which he
can receive more if he pays more
premium so what are you waiting for a
brand new phase of life awaits you with
ICICI Pro guaranteed pension
[Music]
plan